# Ankit Karn

#### Software Engineer 2 - Frontend

🜎 ankitkarnak | 🛅 ankitkarnak | 🏶 ankitkarnportfolio.netlify.app | 🔀 ankit.karn.ak@gmail.com | +919518287083

## SUMMARY

A self-motivated Frontend Developer turned Software Development Engineer 2 (SDE2) with experience in frontend development using NextJS (React) + TypeScript / JavaScript in a product-based startup improving the user experience and increase the efficiency of the application. Started as a fresher and was promoted to SDE2-Frontend after 1.5 years of experience. My responsibilities included implementing KYC/KYB, developing QRIS, Checkout and many more features, writing unit tests to increase code coverage and ensuring the reliability of the code.

# Work Experience

#### SDE-2 Frontend, BUKUWARUNG

April 2023 - Present

- Led the development and scaling of the payments frontend web team.
- Mentored junior intern/fresher developers and provided them with feedback to enhance their skills and knowledge.
- Setup unit tests using JEST to increase code coverage and reduce the number of bugs in the codebase. Also setup Husky hooks to enforce code formatting and linting rules, ensuring a consistent code style across the team

#### Frontend Engineer, BUKUWARUNG

Dec 2021 - March 2023

- Implemented KYC (Know Your Customer) and KYB (Know Your Business) features to enhance the security and compliance of the application. Worked on the Checkout feature to improve the user experience during the payment process.
- Created PPOB (Payment Point Online Bank) WebApp to expand the payment options available to Desktop users.
- Implemented TypeScript in the codebase, resulting in improved code readability and maintainability.

#### Projects

#### RacketMart E-Commerce App Github

https://racketmart.netlify.app

Tech Stack: MERN

• Login/Signup • Add to Cart / Remove from Cart • Increase/Decrease Item Quantity • Add / Remove to Wishlist

### EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp at NeoGCamp

2021

B.Tech: Computer Science And Engineering (CSE) at SIET, Nilokheri

2016 - 2020

# SKILLS

Language or Frameworks: NextJS, ReactJS, TypeScript, JavaScript, ExpressJS

Other Tools and Technologies: SCSS, JEST, Git, GitHub

Last updated: April 18, 2023